{
    "id": "88917bdeb9c54ed6b80dbb13bc349ec0",
    "title": "Prepositions Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The cat is ……………………… the table.",
            "description": "Use on to indicate position on the surface. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "42db3f57ffd54833b0233f2b962812ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "I met him ……………………….. the morning.",
            "description": "Use in with morning, evening etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a582cc499a0d422fb3a030e714a85a42"
        },
        {
            "question": "We met ………………………. a wet Friday.",
            "description": "Use on with days.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "34982f364e9e4d9fb77fd8ae9625e213"
        },
        {
            "question": "We can meet …………………… lunchtime.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fc59d1c53bb3469399f197ade32980fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "Add a little more milk ……………………… the tea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ba1f05e20211480a8fb805a090db0b7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "We can go ……………………….. bus or train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "33fa0eb3cfe24caabeb415c580746d92"
        },
        {
            "question": "She put the coins …………………….. a box.",
            "description": "In shows position inside. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c61497e38e84337a641380971eacf14"
        },
        {
            "question": "Birds live ………………………. nests.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "97e02c640caa49e08f2a0d2ab1cc248d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The injured man was taken …………………………. hospital.",
            "description": "To indicates direction.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ea63e00855a14e479fe465a130663512"
        },
        {
            "question": "Dad was angry when I failed ……………………….. my test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ef04d9ab1ba14affbc9ab8e70010585b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is rude ………………………… everyone.",
            "description": "We use to with expressions like rude, kind, polite, nice, good etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2244abc19dc747e38fd2503478983b02"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you yelling ………………………….. me?",
            "description": "We stare, yell, shout or look at someone. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f88aaf02ce2041ffa9669799a718db5e"
        }
    ]
}